Guide to the New York Foundation For the Arts (NYFA) Records MSS.515
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII. Fiscal Sponsorship, 1971-2011; 52 linear feet in 52 record cartons
  - Subseries C. Artists' Projects, 1982-2011; 36 linear feet in 36 record cartons
    - Goldhuber, Lawrence, 2004-2005 (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Goldwyn, Liz, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - Goldwyn, Liz, 1999-2000 (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - Golub, Jennifer, 1997-1998 (Box 59, Folder 26)
    - Golub, Jennifer, 2000-2004 (Box 59, Folder 27)
    - Gonzalez, Bobby, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 28)
    - Gonzalez, David, 2002-2004 (Box 59, Folder 29)
    - Gonzalez, Diana, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 30)
    - Gonzalez, Larry, 1993-1994 (Box 59, Folder 31)
    - Gonzalez, Maria Elena, 2000-2004 (Box 59, Folder 32)
    - gordon, Coco, 1999-2009 (Box 59, Folder 33)
    - Gordon, Coco, 1999-2009 (Box 59, Folder 34)
    - Gordon, Floyd, 1989-1990 (Box 59, Folder 35)
    - Gordon, Michael, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 36)
    - Gordon, Peter, 1991-1992 (Box 59, Folder 37)
    - Gordon, Robert, 1991-1992 (Box 59, Folder 38)
    - Gorovoy, Jenny, 2001-2002 (Box 59, Folder 39)
    - Goss, Carol, 2000-2005 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Gossels, Lisa, 1997-2004 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Gould, Melissa, 1997-2000 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Grady, Brian, 2010 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Gray, Chadwick/Specter, Laura, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Graham, James, 1995-2000 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Graham, Janet, 1995-1997 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Graham, Janet, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Grant, Chistopher, 2003-2004 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Grant, Chistopher, 2004-2007 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Grant, Paul, 2006-2009 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Gray, Chadwick, 1999-2004 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Gray, Cleve, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Gray, Edward, 1991-1998 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Gray, Edward, 1991-1998 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Gray, Edward, 1991-1998 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Gray, Edward, 1991-1998 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Gray, Edward, 1991-1998 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Greene, Katherine A., 1998-2004 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Greenfield, Amy, 1982-1992 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Greenfield, Amy, 1982-1992 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Greenfield, Amy, 1982-1992 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Greenfield, Amy, 1984-1987 (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Grella, Julia, 2000-2002 (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Gress, Andrew, 2010 (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Greunke, Carol, 1996-2005 (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - Greytak, Sharon, 1987-1990 (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - Greytak, Sharon, 1989-1991 (Box 60, Folder 28)
    - Greytak, Sharon, 1993-1996 (Box 60, Folder 29)
    - Greytak, Sharon, 1998-2005 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Griffin, Charles B., 1999-2004 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Griffin, Paul, 1994-2004 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Griffin, Paul, 1997-2002 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Grist, Ray, 1997-2004 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Gross, Geoffrey, 1999-2005 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Grossman, Joan, 1999-2000 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Groves, Casey, 2005-2006 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Guerra, Roberto, 1998-2005 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Guggenheim, Charles, 1986-1994 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Gunderson, Joanna, 1991-1996 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Gusella, Ernest, 1990 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - GXI, 1993-1995 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Hacker, Melissa, 1990-2004 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Hadleigh-West, Maggie, 1995-1999 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Hadleigh-West, Maggie, 1999-2001 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Haenggi, Andrea, 1999-2004 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Haenggi, Andrea, 2000-2001 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Hall, Tammy F., 1999-2000 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Halpern, John, 2004-2005 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Hamilton, Janine, 1999-2003 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Han, Alice, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Hanrahan, Jerelyn, 1997-2007 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Hanrahan, Jerelyn, 1997-2007 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Hansberry, Caroline, 2000-2007 (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - Hansen, Susan, 1998-2004 (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - Harrell, Trajal, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - Haenggi, Amdrea, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - Harms, Loretta/Solomon, Maury, 1993-2005 (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - Harris, Mary, 1999-2001 (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - Harris, Mary Emma, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 31)
    - Harris, Phyllis, 2003-2005 (Box 61, Folder 32)
    - Harris, Thomas Allen, 2004-2008 (Box 61, Folder 33)
    - Harrison, Joshua, 1988-1990 (Box 61, Folder 34)
    - Harrison, Joshua, 1988-1990 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Harrison, Julie, 1997-2000 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Hart, Amy, 2006-2007 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Harvey, Julie, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Harvey, Julie, 1999-2005 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Hatchett, Yvonne, 1999-2002 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Hattleberg, John, 2002-2005 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Hauser, Ed, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Hay, Mary Ann, 1998-2000 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Hayes, Christopher, 1996-1997 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Haynes, Todd, 1990-1991 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Hays, Sorrel, 1985-1986 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Hays, Sorrel, 1985-1986 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Hays, Sorrel, 1986-1987 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Hays, Sorrel, 1986-1987 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Hays, Sorrel, 1986-1988 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Hays, Sorrel, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Hays, Sorrel, 1989-1991 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Held, Matthias, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Heller, Ben, 1991 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Henderson, Valerie, 2000-2001 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Hendrik, Diane, 1989-1991 (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - Hendrik, Diane, 1990-1992 (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - Herbich, Barbara/Christo, Cyril, 1985-1987 (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - Herbich, Barbara, 1988-1990 (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Herbich, Barbara, 1991 (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - Herbich, Babara, 1998-2009 (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - Herman, Randy, 1984-1986 (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - Herman, Shelly, 1992-1993 (Box 62, Folder 29)
    - Hess, Walter, 1991-2000 (Box 62, Folder 30)
    - Heyward, Julia, 1995-1997 (Box 62, Folder 31)
    - High, Kathryn, 1984-1985 (Box 62, Folder 32)
    - High, Kathryn, 1985-1986 (Box 62, Folder 33)
    - High, Kathryn, 1986-1989 (Box 62, Folder 34)
    - Hill, Peter, 1998-2003 (Box 62, Folder 35)
    - Ho, Cindy, 1997-1999 (Box 62, Folder 36)
    - Ho, Cindy, 1998-2005 (Box 62, Folder 37)
    - Ho, Cindy, 2003-2004 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Hobson, Charles/Williams, John, 1990-1999 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Holder, Elizabeth/Parker, Alexandra, 1999-2002 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Holder, Tracie, 1994, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Holt, Nancy, 1986-1999 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Holt, Norma, 1998-1999 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Holtzman, Elizabeth, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Holzman, David, 2006-2007 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Holzman, Paul, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Happer, Philip, 1996-2004 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Horn, Andrew, 1986-1987 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Horn, Andrew, 1988-1990 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Horschak, Amy, 2006 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Horowitz, Susan, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Horsley, Lori, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Howe, Ilana Weiner, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Hoyt, Satch, 2001-2005 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Hsu, Carleen Ling-an, 2000-2005 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Hsu, Carleen Ling-an, 2000-2005 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Hubatsek, Mark, 2003-2006 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Humes, Immy, 1997-2004 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Hunt, Marilyn, 1993-1995 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Hunt, Paul, 1998-2005 (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Hurlin, Dan, 1996-1999 (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - Hurteau, Paul, 2000-2008 (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - Hwang, Koosil-ja, 1995-2000 (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - Hwang, Koosil-ja, 1996-2002 (Box 63, Folder 27)
    - Hwang, Koosil-ja, 1997-2002 (Box 63, Folder 28)
    - Hwang, Koosil-ja, 1998-2002 (Box 63, Folder 29)
    - Hwang, Koosil-ja, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 30)
    - Hwang, Koosil-ja, 2000-2002 (Box 63, Folder 31)
    - Ibarra, Susie, 2004-2005 (Box 63, Folder 32)
    - Hurwitz, Leo, 1990-1991 (Box 63, Folder 33)
    - Irons, Shaun/Petty, Lauren, 2003-2007 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Irwin, Audrey, 2000-2005 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Irwin, Kim, 2001-2002 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Irvy, Benjamin, 1993 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Irwin, Audrey, 1999 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Jackson, Reginald, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Jacobs, Matthew, 1997 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Jahnke, John, 2000-2004 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Jahnke, John, 2002-2004 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Jahnke, John, 2003-2004 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Janeway, Eliot, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Jansen, Josephine, 1999-2004 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Jarvis, Lucy, 1998-1999 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Jasperse, John, 1996-1998 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Jasperse, John, 1998-1999 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Jesionka, Henry, 1990-1994 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - John, Suki, 1999-2005 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Johnson, Heather, 1999-2004 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Johnson, Marilyn, 1995-2001 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Johnson, Scott, 1986-1992 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Johnston, A. Jane, 2009 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Jisu, Kim, 1999 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Jonas, Joan, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Jones, Carolyn, 1992-1993 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Jones, Patricia, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - Jordan, Michael J., 1999-2005 (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Jordan, Michael J., 1999 (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Joseph, Meryl, 1988-1990 (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Joseph, Meryl, 1989-1998 (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - Joseph, Meryl, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - Joseph, Terese Anne, 1991-1993 (Box 64, Folder 31)
    - Joyce, Billy, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 32)
    - Judson, Nancy, 1998-2000 (Box 64, Folder 33)
    - Kahn, Imani, 1999-2001 (Box 64, Folder 34)
    - Karz, Richard, 1998-2005 (Box 64, Folder 35)
    - Katz, Joel, 1998-2002 (Box 64, Folder 36)
    - Katz, Joel, 1998-2004 (Box 64, Folder 37)
    - Katz, Leandro, 1985-1992 (Box 64, Folder 38)
    - Katz, Leandro, 1992-1999 (Box 64, Folder 39)
    - Katzman, Herbert, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 40)
    - Katzman, Herbert, 1994-2000 (Box 64, Folder 41)
    - Kaufman, Brian, 1994-2004 (Box 64, Folder 42)
    - Kaufman, Brian, 1994-2004 (Box 64, Folder 43)
    - Kaufman, Brian, 1994-2004 (Box 64, Folder 44)
    - Kauman, Brian, 1994-2004 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Kaul, Kavery, 1989-1993 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Kaul, Kavery, 2004-2006 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Kaul, Kavery, 2007-2008 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Kavanagh, William, 1997-2006 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Kavanagh, William, 1997-2006 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Kay, John, 1994-1998 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Kazakov, Rafaelo, 2000-2004 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Kazin, Alfred, 1992-1998 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Kermani, Elise, 1996-2004 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Kerrigan, Caroline, 1998-2004 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Khan, Najmul Saqib, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Kiambouthi, Wairimu, 2003-2005 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Kim, Chee Yun, 1990-1991 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Kim, Yu Yeon, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Kimbrough, Steven, 1988-1999 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - King, John, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - King, John, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - King, Keith, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - King, Keith, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - King, Mallory, 2005-2006 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Kinkead, Gwen, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Kirchheimer, Gloria, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Kirchheimer, Gloria, 1998-2000 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Kirchheimer, Manfred, 1982-2003 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Kirchheimer, Manfred, 1982-2003 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Kirkland, Dep, 1999-2004 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Kirschenbaum, Gayle, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - Kirstein, Ruth Priscilla, 2003-2008 (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Kleinberg, Susan, 2003-2004 (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - Knafo, Robert, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 31)
    - Knaver, Lisa Maya/Levine, Jack, 1987-1988 (Box 65, Folder 32)
    - Knighton, Maurine, 2007-2008 (Box 65, Folder 33)
    - Kach, Alan, 1998-2004 (Box 65, Folder 34)
    - Kogan, Ellen, 1988-1996 (Box 65, Folder 35)
    - Kogan, Ellen, 1988-1996 (Box 65, Folder 36)
    - Kogan, Ellen, 1988-1996 (Box 65, Folder 37)
    - Koos, Anna, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 38)
    - Korda, Susan, 1990-1997 (Box 65, Folder 39)
    - Kotuk, Richard, 1995-1997 (Box 65, Folder 40)
    - Kozak, Ellen, 1995-2002 (Box 65, Folder 41)
    - Kramer, Karen, 1979-1988 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Kramer, Karen, 1983-1987 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Kraus, Chris, 1993-1994 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Kraus, Chris, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Kreitzer, Carson, 1998-2004 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Krementz, Jill, 1998-1999 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Kriendler, Laurie, 1982-1983 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Krosney, Herbert, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Kuntzevich, Richard, 1998-1999 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Kuntzevich, Richard, 2003-2010 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Kupper, Gary, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Lacy, Madison Davis, 2002-2005 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Lacy, Madison Davis, 2002-2005 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Lacy, Madison Davis, 2002-2005 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Laird, Thomas Calvin, 2001-2004 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Lake, Joanna, 2007 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Lamarre, Paul/Waif, Melissa, 1995-2004 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Lance, Mary, 1986-1992 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Lance, Mary, 1986-1992 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Lance, Mary, 1986-1992 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Lance, Mary, 1986-1992 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Lackow, Sandra, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Lance, Mary, 2000-2006 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Lane, Judith, 1999-2002 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Langis, Judith, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Landes, Alison, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Lane, Judith, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - Lanoutte, Jennine, 2002-2004 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - Lavanne, Antonia, 1995-2006 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Leacock, Richard/Woll, Susan, 1984-1985 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Lee, Christopher, 1998-2005 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Lee, Iara, 1994-1996 (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - Lee, In-Ho, 1991-1992 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Lees, Benjamin, 1998-2002 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Lefkowitz, Sandra, 2001-2004 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Lehman, Robin, 1990-1991 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Leichter, Kathy/Skurnik, Jonathan, 1998-2002 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Leichter, Nicholas, 1997-2004 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Lenzer, Don, 1996-2004 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Lenzer, Don, 1997-2004 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Levi, Robert, 1988-2005 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Levi, Robert, 1997-2005 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Levi, Robert, 1997-2007 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Levin, Meryl, 2003-2005 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Levin, Sheila, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Levin, Zaida Booth, 1998-2005 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Levine, Les, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Levitas, Ethan, 1998-2004 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Levitas, Ethan, 1998-2004 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Levitin, Nicholas, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Levy, Frank, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Levy, Owen, 1995-2001 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Libin, Charles, 1987-1988 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Licata, David, 2002-2004 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Lichens, Stan, 1999-2004 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Lichens, Stan, 1999 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Lichtenstein, Adam, 1991-1999 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Lichtenstein, Bill, 1992-1994 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Lichtenstein, Bill, 1997-2006 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Lichtenstein, Bill, 1997-2006 (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - Lichtenstein, Bill, 1997-2006 (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - Lichtenstein, Bill, 1997-2006 (Box 67, Folder 30)
    - Lichtenstein, Bill, 1997-2006 (Box 67, Folder 31)
    - Lichtenstein, Bill, 1997-2006 (Box 67, Folder 32)
    - Lichtenstein, Bill, 1997-2006 (Box 67, Folder 33)
    - Lichtenstein, Bill, 1997-2006 (Box 67, Folder 34)
    - Lichtenstein, Bill, 2002-2006 (Box 67, Folder 35)
    - Lichtenstein, Bill, 2004-2006 (Box 67, Folder 36)
    - Lichtenstein, Bill, 2004-2006 (Box 67, Folder 37)
    - Lidell, Wendy, 1986-1988 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Lidell, Wendy, 1986-1988 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Lieber, Edward, 1993-1994 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Lieber, Edward, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Limperis, Constantine, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Lindfors, Viveca, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Lipsky, Pat/Wiprud, Ted, 1998-2000 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Loewinger, Lawrence, 1992-1995 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Longhi, Jaime/Elliot, Steve, 1998-2001 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Lovejoy, Margot, 2001-2005 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Lovejoy, Margot, 2003-2008 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Lovejoy, Margot, 2003-2008 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Loveland, Karen, 1983-1988 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Luchow, Sandra, 1999-2004 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Ludwich, Julie, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Ludwig, Tiffany, 2003-2008 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Lumpkin, Michael, 1991 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - MacAfee, Norman, 1990-1998 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - MacAfee, Norman, 1998-2004 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - MacDonald, Heather Lyn, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - MacDonald, Heather Lyn, 2000-2005 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - MacDonald, Heather Lyn, 2003-2006 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - MacDonald, Heather Lyn, 2007-2008 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Maciariello, Catherine, 2007-2008 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Mack, Cleo, 2000-2003 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Mack, Cleo, 1999 (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - MacKay, Noreen Ash, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - MacKay, Noreen Ash, 1989-1991 (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - Magierski, Tomasz, 1999-2002 (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - Magierski, Tomasz, 1999-2004 (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - Macgruder, Lewis, 2006 (Box 68, Folder 31)
    - Manhanthappa, Rudresh, 2002-2004 (Box 68, Folder 32)
    - Maharaj, Rajendra Ramoon, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 33)
    - Mahr, Claire, 2005-2006 (Box 68, Folder 34)
    - Major, Chris, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 35)
    - Manin, Steven, 1999 (Box 68, Folder 36)
    - Maloney, William/Schultz, Chiz, 1999-2002 (Box 68, Folder 37)
    - Maloney, William/Schultz, Chiz, 1999-2002 (Box 68, Folder 38)
    - Malinowitz, Harriet, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 39)
    - Loveland, Karen, 1983-1984 (Box 68, Folder 40)
    - Linsley, Johanna, 2006 (Box 68, Folder 41)
    - Manhanthappa, Rudresh, 2005-2006 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Manin, Steve, 1999-2004 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Marcus, Leonard/DeLuca, Maria, 1983-1985 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Marcus, Sharon, 1986-1990 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Marks, Constance, 1993-1996 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Marks, Constance, 1994-1999 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Marlotti, Peter, 2001-2008 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Marlowe, Terri, 2004-2007 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Marshall, Karen, 1999-2009 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Marshall, Karen, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Marucci, Carl J., 2002 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Matalon, Adam, 2002-2009 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Maysles, Albert/Maysles, David, 1985-1990 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Maysles, Albert/Maysles, David, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Maysles, Albert, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Maysles, Albert/Maysles, David, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Maysles, Albert/Corra, Henry, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - McCleave, Leslie, 1996-2006 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - McCleave, Leslie, 1996-2006 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - McCormick, Leslie, 1997-2004 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - McCoy, Ann, 2002-2004 (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - McKean, Rebecca/Winson, Alan, 1998-2009 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Mcleod, Kevin, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - McMannus, Michael, 1981-1983 (Box 69, Folder 24)
    - Medina, David, 1997-1999 (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - Mei, Yin, 1997-2004 (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - Mei, Yin, 1997-2001 (Box 69, Folder 27)
    - Mei, Yin, 2002-2006 (Box 69, Folder 28)
    - Mei, Yin, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 29)
    - Mejias, Justina, 1998-2005 (Box 69, Folder 30)
    - Melamed, Ellen, 1994-2002 (Box 69, Folder 31)
    - MelKonian, Neery, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 32)
    - MelKonian, Neery, 1999-2006 (Box 69, Folder 33)
    - MelKonian, Neery, 1999-2006 (Box 69, Folder 34)
    - Mella, Leanne, 1999-2006 (Box 69, Folder 35)
    - Mermin, Liz/Raskin, Jenny, 1998-1999 (Box 69, Folder 36)
    - Mesa, Nilda, 2001-2008 (Box 69, Folder 37)
    - Michaels Kerry, 1988-1994 (Box 69, Folder 38)
    - Middleton, Andy, 2005-2006 (Box 69, Folder 39)
    - Miller, Eliza, 2000-2001 (Box 69, Folder 40)
    - Miller, Eliza, 2001-2003 (Box 69, Folder 41)
    - Miller, Eliza, 2003-2004 (Box 69, Folder 42)
    - Miller, Eliza, 2005-2007 (Box 69, Folder 43)
    - Miller, Eliza, 2000 (Box 69, Folder 44)
    - Marlotti, Peter, 1997-2002 (Box 69, Folder 45)
    - Miller, Peter, 1998-2001 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Miller, Peter, 2001-2007 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Miller, Peter, 2001-2007 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Miller, Peter, 2002-2003 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Miller, Rebecca, 1997-1999 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Millet, Kate, 1992-1999 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Misch, David, 1983-1990 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Misch, David, 1983-1990 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Mishim, Vladimir, 2004-2008 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Miuccio, Liana, 1997-2004 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Mieczko, Radskaw, 2004 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Mogel, Elizabeth, 2006-2008 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Monson, Jennifer, 2000-2004 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Monson, Jennifer, 2000-2006 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Monson, Jennifer, 2000-2006 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Monson, Jennifer, 2000-2006 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Montejo, Cherry, 2002-2007 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Mookas, Ioannis, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Moran, John, 2002-2005 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Morimoto, Risa, 1999-2005 (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Morimoto, Risa, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Morris, Errol, 1989-1997 (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - Morris, Errol, 1993-1998 (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - Morris, Errol, 1998-2000 (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Morris, Errol, 1998-2004 (Box 70, Folder 25)
    - Morton, Robert, 1997-1999 (Box 70, Folder 26)
    - Mosher, Eve, 2007-2008 (Box 70, Folder 27)
    - Mosher, Eve, 2008-2011 (Box 70, Folder 28)
    - Moss, Dean, 1998-1999 (Box 70, Folder 29)
    - Moss, Dean, 1999-2002 (Box 70, Folder 30)
    - Moss, Dean, 2001-2002 (Box 70, Folder 31)
    - Move, Richard, 2003-2006 (Box 70, Folder 32)
    - Move, Richard, 2005-2006 (Box 70, Folder 33)
    - Mulcahy, Patricia, 2000-2004 (Box 70, Folder 34)
    - Mullen, David, 1998-2000 (Box 70, Folder 35)
    - Mushalla, Michael, 2003-2006 (Box 70, Folder 36)
    - Mycklebust, Scott, 2003-2005 (Box 70, Folder 37)
    - Myerson, Sylvie, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 38)
    - Nadel, Barbara A., 2002-2005 (Box 70, Folder 39)
    - Nader, Nadime, 1993-1999 (Box 70, Folder 40)
    - Nagrin, Lee, 1986-1989 (Box 70, Folder 41)
    - Nagrin, Lee, 1998-2004 (Box 70, Folder 42)
    - Naranjo, Valerie, 1996-1999 (Box 70, Folder 43)
    - Nagrin, Lee, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Nastro, Caroline, 1999-2004 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Nastro, Caroline, 2001-2003 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Nateghi, Benham/Jordan, William, 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Neale, Grant, 2003-2004 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Nissman, Barbara, 1987-1989 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Novek, Minda, 1989-1990 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - O'Day, Kevin, 1997 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - O'Hagan, John, 1995-1997 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - O'Neill, Hugh, 1995-2002 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Oguchi, Tomoko, 2004-2005 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Oguchi, Tomoko, 2008-2009 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Olivé-Bellés, Núria, 2001-2002 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Olugebefola, Ademola, 1997-2004 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Oriól, Willard G., 2000-2004 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Ornitz, Andrea/Briscoe, Carla, 1999-2004 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Owen, Richard, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Paddio, Martin, 1995-1998 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Paddio, Martin, 1995-1998 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Page, Bill, 1993-2005 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Park, Young, 1998-2008 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Pak, Greg, 1996-1999 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Pak, Greg, 1999-2002 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Parent, Dale, 1997-2000 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - Park, Young, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 25)